Staudinger, Hans; Papers ger087
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Correspondence, 1933-1980; 2
  - Triebenstein, Olaf, Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Tyrner-Tyrnauer, Alfred R., Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - re: Wachenheim, Hedwig, Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Wagner, Helmut R., Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Wandel, Eckhard, Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Warburg, Eric, Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Weber, Alfred, Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Weichmann, Herbert, Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Weichmann, Herbert re: Preussenelektra, Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Weil, Herbert, Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Wolfner, Aram, Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Zoff, Otto, Undated (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 24a)
- New School, 1929-1979; 3
  Correspondence and publications dealing with Alvin Johnson and the establishment of the "University in Exile" and important activities of the Graduate School (conferences, anniversary celebrations, refugee assistance projects, etc.).
  - Johnson, Alvin, Undated (Box 4 (3-New School), Folder 25-26)
  - Johnson, Alvin, 1924 (Box 4 (3-New School), Folder 27)
  - Johnson, Alvin, Undated (Box 4 (3-New School), Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 4 (3-New School), Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 1953-1963 (Box 4 (3-New School), Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 4 (3-New School), Folder 31)
  - 25th anniversary, 1959 (Box 4 (3-New School), Folder 32)
  - Middle States evaluation, 1960 (Box 4 (3-New School), Folder 33)
  - Progress report, 1961 (Box 4 (3-New School), Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 4 (3-New School), Folder 35)
  - Birenbaum - Remarks... Faculty notice re: smoking, 1962 (Box 4 (3-New School), Folder 36)
  - Progress report, 1962 (Box 4 (3-New School), Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 4 (3-New School), Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 4 (3-New School), Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 4 (3-New School), Folder 40)
  - 40th anniversary, Undated (Box 4 (3-New School), Folder 41-43)
  - 40th anniversary - Arnold Brecht Henry Kissinger, Undated (Box 4 (3-New School), Folder 44)
  - 40th anniversary - Bonn conference, Undated (Box 4 (3-New School), Folder 45)
  - 40th anniversary, Undated (Box 4 (3-New School), Folder 46)
  - 40th anniversary - Bonn conference, Undated (Box 4 (3-New School), Folder 47-48)
  - 40th anniversary Graduate Faculty (University in Exile) Background information, Undated (Box 4 (3-New School), Folder 49)
  - 40th anniversary, Undated (Box 4 (3-New School), Folder 40-51)
  - 40th anniversary - Heuss Chair - Bonn Conference, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 1)
  - 40th anniversary - Bonn Conference - Heuss Chair, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 2)
  - 40th anniversary - Heuss Chair, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 3)
  - 40th anniversary - Ludz, Peter D., Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 5)
  - Greenbaum, Joseph, 1975 January-1975 March (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 7)
  - Marshall Fund, 1975 (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 10-11)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 12)
  - Addresses - Lists, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 13)
  - Alumni, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 14)
  - American-European Institute, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 15)
  - Art Collection and Exhibition Exiled French scholart in America Erotic Art, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 16)
  - Board of Trustees, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 17)
  - Board of Visitors, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 18)
  - Budget, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 19)
  - Cadoret, Michel, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 20)
  - Caribbean Cruise, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 21)
  - Conference on Weimar Germany, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 22)
  - Conference on the Meaning of Citizenship, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 23)
  - David, Henry, Dean, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 24)
  - Doctoral review, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 25)
  - Endowment Fund Campaign, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 26)
  - Everett, John R., Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 27)
  - Faculty - Correspondence with State Department, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 28)
  - Faculty, 1969; 1979 (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 29)
  - Fund drive - University-in-Exile Fund, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 30)
  - Greenbaum, Joseph, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 31)
  - Heuss, Chair, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 32)
  - Hosiosky, Issai, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 33)
  - Invitations, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 34)
  - Mayer, Albert, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 35)
  - Mayer, Carl, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 36)
  - Paschal Fund, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 37)
  - The Philosophy Department, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 38)
  - Publications (Catalogs, bibliographies, etc), Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 39)
  - Refugee assistance, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 40)
  - Reifferscheidt Scholarship, Undated (Box 5 (3-New School), Folder 41)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 6 (3-New School), Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 6 (3-New School), Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Correspondence - Public Health, Undated (Box 6 (3-New School), Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller-Foundation - Letters of regret, Undated (Box 6 (3-New School), Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Cases, reports, Undated (Box 6 (3-New School), Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Monthly statements, Undated (Box 6 (3-New School), Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Markinsky, Undated (Box 6 (3-New School), Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, Undated (Box 6 (3-New School), Folder 8-10)
  - Simons, Hans, Undated (Box 6 (3-New School), Folder 11)
  - Social Research, Undated (Box 6 (3-New School), Folder 12)
  - Students' addresses, Undated (Box 6 (3-New School), Folder 13)
  - Study Center in Community Participation, Undated (Box 6 (3-New School), Folder 14-17)
  - Study Center in Community Participation on Education for Participation, 1955 June 23 (Box 6 (3-New School), Folder 18)
  - Study Center in Community Participation, Undated (Box 6 (3-New School), Folder 19-21)
  - White, Howard B., Undated (Box 6 (3-New School), Folder 22)
- Organizations and Associations, Undated; 4
  Correspondence; publications of the groups.
  - American Council for Emigrés in the Professions, Undated (Box 6 (4-Organizations and Associations), Folder 23-24)
  - American Council for Emigrés in the Professions - J. Jefferson, Undated (Box 6 (4-Organizations and Associations), Folder 25)
  - American Council for Emigrés in the Professions - Anni Gottschalk, Undated (Box 6 (4-Organizations and Associations), Folder 26)
  - American Council ... re: Alvin Johnson, Undated (Box 6 (4-Organizations and Associations), Folder 27)
  - American Council ..., Undated (Box 6 (4-Organizations and Associations), Folder 28)
  - American Council ... Stiftung Volkswagenwerk, Undated (Box 6 (4-Organizations and Associations), Folder 29)
  - American Council on Germany, Undated (Box 6 (4-Organizations and Associations), Folder 30)
  - Conference Group on German Politics, Undated (Box 6 (4-Organizations and Associations), Folder 31)
  - Deutsches Theater, Undated (Box 6 (4-Organizations and Associations), Folder 32-35)
  - German Society of the City of New York, Undated (Box 7 (4-Organizations and Associations), Folder 1)
  - Goethe Institute, Undated (Box 7 (4-Organizations and Associations), Folder 2)
  - Institut für Zeitgeschichte, Undated (Box 7 (4-Organizations and Associations), Folder 3)
  - Inter Nationes, Undated (Box 7 (4-Organizations and Associations), Folder 4-5)
  - League for Industrial Democracy, Undated (Box 7 (4-Organizations and Associations), Folder 6)
  - Leo Baeck Institute, Undated (Box 7 (4-Organizations and Associations), Folder 7-8)
  - Marshall (Plan, Fund, Foundation), Undated (Box 7 (4-Organizations and Associations), Folder 9)
  - Medical Research Foundation, Undated (Box 7 (4-Organizations and Associations), Folder 10)
  - Metropolitan Economic Association, Undated (Box 7 (4-Organizations and Associations), Folder 11)
  - New Democratic Club, Undated (Box 7 (4-Organizations and Associations), Folder 12)
  - Newark House, Undated (Box 7 (4-Organizations and Associations), Folder 13)
  - Selfhelp, Undated (Box 7 (4-Organizations and Associations), Folder 14)
  - Selfhelp - Schindler, Undated (Box 7 (4-Organizations and Associations), Folder 15)
- Writings, speeches, etc., Undated; 5
  Typescripts of articles, books, speeches, and book reviews.
  - Writings, 1935 (Box 7 (5-Writings, speeches, etc.), Folder 16)
  - Die Emanzipationsbewegungen der Jugend bis zu den terroristen, Undated (Box 7 (5-Writings, speeches, etc.), Folder 17)
  - The Farm by the Lake, Undated (Box 7 (5-Writings, speeches, etc.), Folder 18)
  - Die Neue Geplante Wirtshaftspolitik der Verenigten Staaten, Undated (Box 7 (5-Writings, speeches, etc.), Folder 19)
  - On the German Organization of Coal Production and Distribution, Undated (Box 7 (5-Writings, speeches, etc.), Folder 20)
  - Research projects, Undated (Box 7 (5-Writings, speeches, etc.), Folder 21)
  - Shirer, William. The Rise and Fall of the Third Reich, Undated (Box 7 (5-Writings, speeches, etc.), Folder 22)
  - Speech to the Graduate Faculty, Undated (Box 7 (5-Writings, speeches, etc.), Folder 23)
  - State and Economic Systems, Part 1, Undated (Box 7 (5-Writings, speeches, etc.), Folder 24)
  - State and Economic Systems, Part 2, Undated (Box 7 (5-Writings, speeches, etc.), Folder 25)
  - Die Wirtschaft der Offentlichen Hand, Undated (Box 7 (5-Writings, speeches, etc.), Folder 26)
  - Big Business, Undated (Box 7 (5-Writings, speeches, etc.), Folder 27)
  - Booklists, Undated (Box 7 (5-Writings, speeches, etc.), Folder 28-29)
  - (Clippings], Undated (Box 7 (5-Writings, speeches, etc.), Folder 30)
  - Common Market, Undated (Box 7 (5-Writings, speeches, etc.), Folder 31)
  - Economic Forecasts, Undated (Box 7 (5-Writings, speeches, etc.), Folder 32)
  - Economic Policy, Undated (Box 7 (5-Writings, speeches, etc.), Folder 33-46)
- Lectures and notes, 1945-1968; 6
  Drafts and texts of lectures; notes; reading lists; clippings and background materials.
  - Economic Policy - General, Undated (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 1)
  - Economic Policy - Alexander Pekelis, Undated (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 2)
  - Economic Policy Applied Economics Seminar, Undated (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 3)
  - Economic Policy Comparative economic policies, Undated (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 4)
  - Economic Policy Employment Bill of 1945, Undated (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 5)
  - Economic Policy Employment Act of 1946, Undated (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 6-7)
  - Economic Policy Employment Act of 1946 Analysis, Undated (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 8)
  - Economic Policy - How to make comparisons, Undated (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 9)
  - Economic Policy - Output of a hypothetical economy, Undated (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 10)
  - Economic Policy - Price comparison, Undated (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 11)
  - Economic Policy - Trade, Undated (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 12)
  - Economic Policy - Class material, 1957-1958 (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 13)
  - Economic Policy, 1962-1963 (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 14)
  - Economic Policy, 1965 Fall (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 15)
  - Economic Policy - Reading lists, 1966 Spring (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 16)
  - Economic Policy, 1968 (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 17)
  - Everett Speech, Undated (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 18)
  - Multinationals speech, Undated (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 19)
  - The New Border Line Between State Economy and Market Economy, Undated (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 20)
  - Public Organization, Undated (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 21)
  - Questions and Problems Concerning the Use of Budgetary, Short-run, and Economic, Undated (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 22)
    Subseries Projections and Their Adaptations.
  - Social Psychology of Effective Citizenship, Undated (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 23)
  - Vorlassene Forschungen, Undated (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 24)
  - Unidentified, Undated (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 25-46)
  - Unidentified - Letter to Neisser, Undated (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 47)
  - Economic Policy - Books, Undated (Box 8 (6-Lectures and notes), Folder 48)
- Subjects: Individuals, Undated; 7
  Publications of individuals; photographs and correspondence. (See also "Series 2 - Correspondence" and other appropriate series for additional items of correspondence.).
  - Arendt, Hannah, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 1)
  - Bell, Daniel - Cultural Contradictions, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 2)
  - Bell, Daniel, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 3)
  - Bernstein, Peter, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 4)
  - Brandt, Karl, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 5)
  - Brandt, Willy, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 6-7)
  - Braunthal, Alfred, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 8)
  - Brecht, Arnold, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 9-10)
  - Breslauer, George, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 11)
  - Brown, Elizabeth A. R., Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 12)
  - Brüning, Heinrich, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 13)
  - Clague,Evan, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 14)
  - Edschmid, Kasimir, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 15)
  - Fetscher, Iring, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 16)
  - Galbraith, John Kenneth, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 17-19)
  - Gideonse, Harry, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 20)
  - Greene, Murray, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 21)
  - Grossman, Kurt R., Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 22)
  - Gurwitsch, Aron, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 23)
  - Halasi, Albert, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 24)
  - Halle, Ida J., Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 25)
  - Heimann, Eduard, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 26)
  - Heineman, Dannie N., Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 27)
  - Henle, Mary, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 28)
  - Heuss, Theodor, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 29-31)
  - Hirsch, Julius, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 32-33)
  - Hirsch, Julius, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 1-3)
  - Hirsch, Felix, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 4)
  - Holborn, Hajo, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 5)
  - Honigsheim, Paul, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 6-7)
  - Hula, Erich, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 8)
  - Israeli, Nathan, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 9)
  - Jonas, Hans, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 10-11)
  - Kallen, Horace M., Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 12)
  - Kaufmann, Felix, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 13)
  - Koyre, Alexandre, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 14)
  - Kris, Ernst, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 15)
  - Landmann, Julius, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 16)
  - Lederer, Emil, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 17)
  - Lerner, Abba P., Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 18)
  - Mackauer, Christian W., Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 19)
  - Mannheim Karl, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 20)
  - Melamid, Alexander, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 21)
  - Menko, Dietrich, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 22)
  - Neisser, Hans, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 23)
  - Nelson, Benjamin, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 24)
  - Ornati, Oscar A., Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 25)
  - Pekelis, Alexander, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 26)
  - Rabi, Isidor Isaac, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 27)
  - Rogosin, I., Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 28)
  - Rustow, Alexander, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 29-32)
  - Salmon, Albert, Undated (Box 11 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 1-5)
  - Salomon Janovsky, Hannah, Undated (Box 11 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 6)
  - Schiller, Karl, Undated (Box 11 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 7)
  - Schutz, Alfred, Undated (Box 11 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 8)
  - Sonne, Hans Christian, Undated (Box 11 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 9)
  - Speier, Hans, Undated (Box 11 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 10)
  - Spier, Fred S., Undated (Box 11 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 11)
  - Steltzer, Theodor, Undated (Box 11 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 12)
  - Sternberg, Fritz, Undated (Box 11 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 13)
  - Stolper, Gustav, Undated (Box 11 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 14-15)
  - Tenbruck, Friedrich H., Undated (Box 11 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 16)
  - Tillich, Paul, Undated (Box 11 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 17-18)
  - Vidich,,Arthur J., Undated (Box 11 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 19-21)
  - Wadmond, Lowell, Undated (Box 11 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 22)
  - Warburg, James P., Undated (Box 11 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 23)
  - Weber, Max, Undated (Box 11 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 24)
  - Weichmann, Herbert, Undated (Box 11 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 25)
  - Wertheimer, Max, Undated (Box 11 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 26)
  - Willkie, Wendell L., Undated (Box 11 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 27)
  - Wunderlich, Frieda, Undated (Box 11 (7-Subjects: Individuals), Folder 28)
- Teaching and research materials, 1968-1979; Undated; 8
  Pamphlets, clippings, and some correspondence on the specific topic.
  - Bureaucracy, Undated (Box 12 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 1-2)
  - Business and Government, Undated (Box 12 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 3-8)
  - Common Market, Undated (Box 12 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 9-12)
  - The Cooper Union Centennial, Undated (Box 12 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 13-14)
  - Democracy, Undated (Box 12 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 15-16)
  - Ecology, Undated (Box 12 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 17-19)
  - Ecology, Undated (Box 13 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 1-3)
  - Economics (General), Undated (Box 13 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 4-17)
  - Economics (General) - Adolph Lowe Symposium, Undated (Box 13 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 18-32)
  - Economics (General) - Adolph Lowe Symposium Heilbroner, Robert, Undated (Box 14 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 1-10)
  - Economic growth, Undated (Box 14 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 11-15)
  - Economic policies, Undated (Box 14 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 16-21)
  - Economic theory, Undated (Box 14 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 22)
  - Economic theory - Forecasting, Undated (Box 14 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 23)
  - Education, Undated (Box 14 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 24-26)
  - Education, Undated (Box 15 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 1-4)
  - Education - Authority crisis, Undated (Box 15 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 5)
  - Education - Students, Undated (Box 15 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 6-17)
  - Education - University reform, Undated (Box 15 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 18-20)
  - Education - Wandervögel, Undated (Box 15 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 21)
  - Education - Youth and terror, Undated (Box 15 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 22-25)
  - Electricity, Undated (Box 16 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 1)
  - Electricity - Kraftwerk Staudinger, Undated (Box 16 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 2-4)
  - Electricity - Preussenelektra, Undated (Box 16 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 5)
  - Electricity - Preussen Elektra, Undated (Box 16 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 6-8)
  - Electricity - VEBA, Undated (Box 16 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 9-12)
  - Energy - General, Undated (Box 16 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 13)
  - Energy - Coal, Undated (Box 16 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 14-18)
  - Energy - Oil, Undated (Box 16 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 19-23)
  - Equal employment, Undated (Box 16 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 24)
  - Exil als Heimat, Undated; manuscript (Box 16 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 25)
  - Family, Undated (Box 16 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 26)
  - Foreign affairs (General), Undated (Box 16 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 27-30)
  - Foreign affairs (General), Undated (Box 17 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 1)
  - Foreign affairs (General), Undated (Box 17 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 2-6)
  - Foreign affairs - Africa, Undated (Box 17 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 7)
  - Foreign affairs - Asia, Undated (Box 17 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 8)
  - Foreign affairs - Asia - Japan, Undated (Box 17 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 9-10)
  - Foreign affairs - Canada, Undated (Box 17 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 11)
  - Foreign Affairs Europe, Undated (Box 17 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 12-14)
  - Foreign affairs - Europe - Germany, Undated (Box 17 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 15)
  - Foreign affairs - Europe - Netherlands, Undated (Box 17 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 16)
  - Foreign affairs - Europe - Italy, Undated (Box 17 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 17)
  - Foreign affairs - Europe - Sweden, Undated (Box 17 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 18)
  - Foreign affairs - Near East, Undated (Box 17 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 19)
  - Foreign affairs - World federation, Undated (Box 17 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 20)
  - Foreign trade, Undated (Box 17 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 21-23)
  - Geography - Physical, Economic, Political, Undated (Box 17 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 24)
  - Germany, Undated (Box 17 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 25-31)
  - Geography, Undated (Box 18 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 1)
  - Germany DDR, Undated (Box 18 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 2)
  - Germany - Economics, Undated (Box 18 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 3-18)
  - Germany - Politics, Undated (Box 18 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 19-22)
  - Germany - SPD, Undated (Box 18 (8-Teaching and research materials), Folder 23-27)